(Emily:)All right.
(Penny:)It has also been shown to cause
(Penny:)significantly fewer side effects
than other oral contraceptives.
(Penny:)Although it can cause acne,
which, if you ask me, kind of
(Penny:)increases its effectiveness
as a contraceptive.
(Emily:)Funny.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm sorry. Did we get off
on the wrong foot?
(Penny:)Because since the other
night, I kind of feel like
(Penny:)you might have a problem
with me.
(Emily:)No, it's fine.
(Penny:)Are you sure,
because it doesn't seem fine?
(sighs)
Okay.
(Emily:)If you really want
to talk about this,
(Emily:)I do have a problem.
(Penny:)Oh, my God.
Tell me-- what did I do?
(Emily:)Look, it's nothing. It's just...
(Emily:)Raj told me that a while ago,
you two hooked up.
What?! Oh, why
would he say that?
(Emily:)Did it not happen?
(Penny:)Well, I wouldn't exactly
call it a hook-up.
(Emily:)Did you kiss?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Emily:)Were you naked?
So, it was a hook-up.
(Leonard:)No.